export default [
{
            id: 1,
            question: 'What is 2 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['4','6','3','5'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is 2 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['5','8','6','7'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 3,
            question: 'What is 2 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['10','8','7','9'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 4,
            question: 'What is 2 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['11','9','12','10'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 5,
            question: 'What is 2 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['12','11','14','13'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 6,
            question: 'What is 2 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['13','14','16','15'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 7,
            question: 'What is 2 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['15','17','16','18'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 8,
            question: 'What is 3 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['6','7','9','8'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is 3 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['9','10','11','12'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 10,
            question: 'What is 3 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['13','12','15','14'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 11,
            question: 'What is 3 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['17','15','16','18'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 12,
            question: 'What is 3 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['18','19','20','21'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 13,
            question: 'What is 3 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['24','22','21','23'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 14,
            question: 'What is 3 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['26','24','25','27'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 15,
            question: 'What is 4 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['10','11','12','9'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 16,
            question: 'What is 4 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['13','15','14','16'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 17,
            question: 'What is 4 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['17','19','18','20'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 18,
            question: 'What is 4 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['24','22','21','23'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 19,
            question: 'What is 4 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['26','25','28','27'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 20,
            question: 'What is 4 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['30','31','29','32'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 21,
            question: 'What is 4 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['33','35','36','34'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 22,
            question: 'What is 5 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['12','13','15','14'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 23,
            question: 'What is 5 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['20','19','17','18'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 24,
            question: 'What is 5 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['22','23','24','25'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 25,
            question: 'What is 5 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['29','27','28','30'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 26,
            question: 'What is 5 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['35','32','33','34'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 27,
            question: 'What is 5 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['38','39','40','37'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 28,
            question: 'What is 5 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['43','45','44','42'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 29,
            question: 'What is 6 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['15','18','16','17'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 30,
            question: 'What is 6 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['24','23','22','21'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 31,
            question: 'What is 6 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['30','27','29','28'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 32,
            question: 'What is 6 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['33','35','36','34'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 33,
            question: 'What is 6 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['41','42','39','40'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 34,
            question: 'What is 6 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['45','48','47','46'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 35,
            question: 'What is 6 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['51','54','52','53'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 36,
            question: 'What is 7 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['18','20','19','21'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 37,
            question: 'What is 7 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['26','28','25','27'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 38,
            question: 'What is 7 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['35','33','34','32'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 39,
            question: 'What is 7 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['40','41','42','39'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 40,
            question: 'What is 7 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['46','48','49','47'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 41,
            question: 'What is 7 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['55','54','53','56'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 42,
            question: 'What is 7 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['60','62','61','63'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 43,
            question: 'What is 3 x 2 ?',
            answers: ['6','3','5','4'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 44,
            question: 'What is 3 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['9','7','8','6'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 45,
            question: 'What is 3 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['9','12','10','11'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 46,
            question: 'What is 3 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['15','13','12','14'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 47,
            question: 'What is 3 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['17','16','15','18'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 48,
            question: 'What is 3 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['19','20','18','21'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 49,
            question: 'What is 4 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['9','10','12','11'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 50,
            question: 'What is 4 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['16','13','14','15'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 51,
            question: 'What is 4 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['18','20','17','19'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 52,
            question: 'What is 4 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['23','24','21','22'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 53,
            question: 'What is 4 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['28','27','26','25'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 54,
            question: 'What is 5 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['13','14','15','12'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 55,
            question: 'What is 5 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['20','18','19','17'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 56,
            question: 'What is 5 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['22','25','24','23'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 57,
            question: 'What is 5 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['30','28','27','29'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 58,
            question: 'What is 5 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['34','32','33','35'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 59,
            question: 'What is 6 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['16','17','15','18'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 60,
            question: 'What is 6 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['22','24','21','23'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 61,
            question: 'What is 6 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['30','27','28','29'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 62,
            question: 'What is 6 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['34','36','35','33'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 63,
            question: 'What is 6 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['40','42','41','39'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 64,
            question: 'What is 7 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['20','21','19','18'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 65,
            question: 'What is 7 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['28','26','25','27'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 66,
            question: 'What is 7 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['32','33','34','35'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 67,
            question: 'What is 7 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['39','40','42','41'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 68,
            question: 'What is 7 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['48','47','49','46'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 69,
            question: 'What is 8 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['21','23','24','22'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 70,
            question: 'What is 8 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['29','30','31','32'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 71,
            question: 'What is 8 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['37','39','38','40'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 72,
            question: 'What is 8 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['47','48','46','45'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 73,
            question: 'What is 8 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['53','54','55','56'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 74,
            question: 'What is 9 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['24','25','26','27'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 75,
            question: 'What is 9 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['33','34','36','35'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 76,
            question: 'What is 9 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['44','42','43','45'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 77,
            question: 'What is 9 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['52','51','53','54'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 78,
            question: 'What is 9 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['63','61','62','60'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
]
